http://www.svf.net/index.php/literature/privacy-policy

ISO 9001:2015 CertifiedDon’t Miss Our New Webinar Series! Click Here to Join Now!
SVF Flow Controls is classified as an Essential Business and is still processing orders. Read our announcement HERE
SIDE BAR
×
HomeProduct LibraryValve LibraryAccessoriesValves by Category »»Hygienic "CleanFLOW" ValvesSanitary - "CleanTECH" ValvesHigh Pressure SeriesDirect Mount SeriesIndustrial SeriesButterfly SeriesFlanged SeriesFire Safe Ball ValvesV-Port Control ValvesInstrumentation Ball ValvesAlloy ValvesThree Way Ball ValvesMetal Seated Ball ValvesFull Port ValvesStandard Port ValvesValves by Application »»Hygienic SeriesHigh Pressure SeriesProcess-Quality SeriesSteam & Thermal FluidsOil & Gas ValvesCNG ValvesChemical Applications »»Chlorine ValvesHydrogen Peroxide ValvesCryogenic ValvesActuators & More »»ActuatorsControlsAccessoriesControls & More »»ControlsPositionersLimit SwitchesPilot ValvesActuatorsAccessoriesAccessories »»ActuatorsControlsOther AccessoriesEngineering ResourcesResource LibraryEngineering Tech BriefsWhite PapersWiring DiagramsCertificatesActuator Sizing GuideCv and Flow CalculatorSVF Video Channel Questions? "Ask The Experts"Documents/Literature Valve Data SheetsActuators & Controls Data SheetsUser Manuals (IOM's)Product/Sales BrochuresTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyAbout usContact UsU.S. & Canada Sales & SupportLatin America & Spain Sales & SupportQuestions? "Ask The Experts"Webinar
Search ...
Home
Product Library
Valve Library
Accessories
Valves by Category »»
Hygienic "CleanFLOW" Valves
Sanitary - "CleanTECH" Valves
High Pressure Series
Direct Mount Series
Industrial Series
Butterfly Series
Flanged Series
Fire Safe Ball Valves
Standard Port Valves
Valves by Application »»
Hygienic Series
High Pressure Series
Process-Quality Series
Steam & Thermal Fluids
Oil & Gas Valves
CNG Valves
Chemical Applications »»
Chlorine Valves
Hydrogen Peroxide Valves
Cryogenic Valves
Actuators & More »»
Actuators
Controls
Accessories
Controls & More »»
Controls
Positioners
Limit Switches
Pilot Valves
Actuators
Accessories
Accessories »»
Actuators
Controls
Other Accessories
Engineering Resources
Resource Library
Engineering Tech Briefs
White Papers
Wiring Diagrams
Certificates
Actuator Sizing Guide
Cv and Flow Calculator
SVF Video Channel
Questions? "Ask The Experts"
Documents/Literature
Valve Data Sheets
Actuators & Controls Data Sheets
User Manuals (IOM's)
Product/Sales Brochures
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
About us
Contact Us
U.S. & Canada Sales & Support
Latin America & Spain Sales & Support
Questions? "Ask The Experts"
Webinar
Privacy Policy
HomeDocuments/LiteraturePrivacy Policy
Details
Print
Email
Effective: April 15, 2005 - Updated January 29, 2018 by SVF Flow Controls, LLC
SVF Flow Controls, LLC (SVF) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website and will not sell or provide any Non-Public Personal Information to anyone without your permission.
Types of Information Cookies. A Cookie is a randomly generated unique number placed on your computer. It allows us to identify your computer without requiring your disclosure of any Non-Public Personal Information. Cookies make it possible to both store and retrieve information through your internet browser. A Cookie itself cannot read information off a hard drive or read Cookie files from other sites. General Information is information that does not itself reveal your identity. General Information may include, without limitation: generic business type; SIC code; information derived from publicly available databases (such as Dun and Bradstreet); user behavior on our website; and aggregated generic information.
Non-Public Personal Information is any non-public information you provide to us or our Partners that is proprietary or identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate you or someone at your business. Non-Public Personal Information may include, without limitation: name; address; phone number; e-mail address; credit card number; account information; voting behavior; spending patterns; and individual tastes and preferences.
Partners are individuals or entities we engage to help us carry out our mission. What information we collect. SVF collects general information and Non-Public Personal Information.
How we collect our information. SVF collects general information through the use of cookies and server-based tracking systems to view the usage of the website. Non-Public Personal Information is collected through registration or contact forms on this site and will never be used for any purpose other than internal use or by our Partners unless the registrant chooses to be added to mailing lists (this is a choice made by the registrant on the Registration form). Privacy Policy changes. Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted here on our website.
Changing your non-public personal information. SVF provides you with the opportunity to change your Non-Public Personal Information online for all registration information. Please contact SVF to change any Non-Public Personal Information provided to us through a contact form.
If you have any questions or concerns about any privacy issues, please contact us.
Links
Valve Data SheetsActuators & Controls Data SheetsUser Manuals (IOM's)Product/Sales BrochuresTerms and ConditionsPrivacy Policy
Stay On Track!
Click Here to StayConnected with SVF
Website Maintenance by the Graphics Design Department of SVF Flow Controls, LLC.
